彼は仕方なく王子になった
この王様のいない世界で
少なくとも私達の希望する明日は
だから彼は不本意ながらも王子であろうとした
その秘密を私はまだ知らない
Callin' out to all
Here am I, lost and found...
A dying scream makes no sound
Callin' out to all that I've ever known
とはいえ、彼は一体どうやって王子になったのだろうか
We live a dying dream...
誰かが「王子」というなの
生け贄になることでしかやってこないと気づいていたから
He had no choice but to become a prince.
If you know what I mean...
At any rate,
It's all that I've ever known...
he realized that a scapegoat known as a "prince" is needed to usher in the future we hope for.
It's all that I've ever known
That's why he became a prince, although reluctantly.
Catch the wheel that breaks a butterfly
In this world where kings don't even exist...
Cry the rain that fills the ocean wide
Just how did he become a prince?
I still haven't uncovered that secret.
I tried to talk with God to no avail
Calling him up in-and-out of nowhere
I said if you won't save me
Please don't waste my time
http://animetranscripts.wikispaces.com
Well, here we are, Miss.
Well, here we are, miss.
And here's your bag.
ここが… 世界の中心なの？
This is...
...the center of the world?
Episode 1
I've Found Myself a Prince
It's not quite like how I imagined it.
なんか、想像してたのと違う
噴水も思ってたより全然遠いし
The fountain's further in than I thought as well.
Washington DC
Baltimore, Annapolis, Philadelphia
みんな怒ってるかな
I wonder if the others will be angry...
大杉君、携帯つけてたら絶対かけてくるよね
Oosugi-kun will definitely call me if he's got a cellphone with him.
Since I came all the way here, I must achieve my goal.
せっかくここまで来たんだから、目的は果たさなきゃ
I missed...
ダメー、遠すぎるよ
It's too far away...
Hey! Young lady, what did you just throw?
Hey, you wanna die?!
Hey! You wanna die!?
Hey, are you okay?
おーい、君！ 大丈夫？
Eh?! Is he for real?!
マジ？！
Why is he stark naked?
っていうか、なんで全裸なの？
Number 9 is more special than I imagined him to be.
ナンバー９は想像していた以上にユニークな男だな
だがここで終わりだ
But this is the end for him.
そうですか。少々惜しい気も致します
Is that so?
That's somewhat unfortunate.
Are you siding with him?
君は彼の味方か？
嫉妬するね、ジュイス
That makes me jealous, Juiz.
Prepare for my return.
帰国の準備を
Yes. Please continue your work as a Savior.
はい。では今後も救世主たらんことを
ううぅ、寒っ！
I'm freezing!
Come to think of it, I'm naked...
ていうか、裸だし
A cellphone... and a pistol?!
携帯に… 拳銃？！
ホワイトハウス…
The White House?
ホワイトハウスは分かるのに、自分が誰なのか分かんないし
I recognize the White House, but I don't remember who I am.
Hey! Young lady, what did you just throw?
Hey, you wanna die?!
Hey! You wanna die!?
Hey, are you okay?
おーい、君！ 大丈夫？
Wait, I'm the one who's in more danger...
つーか、俺がヤバいじゃん？
轢かれた？
Did he get run over?!
Get that guy!
I'll use this chance to escape.
今のうちに…
うそ！
No way!
危なかったね、君、今のうちに逃げた方がいいよ
That looked pretty dangerous.
You'd best take this chance to run away.
I-I'm not in any danger...
あ、危なくないし
でも、ホワイトハウスに向かって何か投げたらマズイでしょ？
But throwing something at the White House isn't the appropriate thing to do, right?
見てたんですか？
You saw that?
まあね
Sort of.
Thanks.
ありがとう
あの、寒くないんですか？
Um... Aren't you cold?
I am.
寒いよ
あの、これ、貸してあげる
Um... I'll lend this to you.
いいの？
Is this okay? I've got to run off too.
俺も逃げなきゃならないけど
It's fine. Regard this as a "thank you" for helping me out.
いいよ
助けてくれたお礼
Thanks. I won't hesitate then.
ありがとう
じゃあ、遠慮なく
じゃあ！
Bye!
マッサラじゃんか！
It's totally empty.
なんかないのかよ 俺が誰だか分かる記録
Isn't there anything on here that will tell me who I am?
Hello, this is Juiz.
はい、ジュイスです
ジュイス？ 誰、君？
Juiz? Who are you?
あなたのコンシェルジュです
I'm your concierge.
I thought that you were going to fade out  just like that.
あのままフェイドアウトかと思いました
無事だったようですね
It seems that you're okay, though.
Hey... Do you know who I am?
君さ、俺のこと、誰だか知ってるの？
誰か？
Who?
Move out!
今回初めて記憶を消すにあたり
This is the first time your memories have been erased,
and since I didn't receive any instructions to prepare a new identity for you,
新しい経歴を用意しろとの指示がありませんでしたので
I don't know who you are right now.
今あなたが誰かということは分かりかねますが
記憶を消す！？
My memories were erased?!
The last instructions given to me were to tell you where you are supposed to go next.
最後の指示では次に向かう場所だけを伝えろとのことでしたので
そちらをお送り致します
I'm sending the details to you now.
Well then, good luck.
では、健闘をお祈りしつつ
We sincerely hope that you'll continue to work as a Savior.
あなたが今後も救世主たらんことを切に願います
My home is over there?
これって、俺の家ってことかな
That was scary... What happened just now?
怖かった… 何だったの、あれ
Guess I shouldn't do things I'm not used to.
やっぱり慣れないことするもんじゃないな
やばっ！ パスポート！
Oh no! My passport!
What should I do...
どうしよう
上着のポケットだ
It's in my coat pocket.
Hey there!
やー、こんちは！
確かにこの格好じゃなあ…
Well, I do look a bit weird...
What should I do...?
どうしよう
絶対取り返さなきゃ
I have to get it back!
That way.
There he is!
いた！
How the heck did he borrow a pair of pants?
何でズボン貸すわけ？
I don't know what's going on...
わけ分かんないし
Um...!
あのー！
Wait up!
ちょっと！ すみませーん！
Excuse me!
ここか？
This is the place?
No way! Where did he go?
え、うそ？ どこ？
U-Um...
あ、あの！
Hello.
こんにちは
Hey.
Dude, what do you think you're doing?
ねえ、俺の部屋って二階だったよな
Hey, my room is on the second floor, right?
Aren't you in room B on the third floor?
Oh crap, oh crap!
やばいよ、やばいよ
急がないと飛行機に乗れなくなっちゃう！
I won't make it in time for my flight if I don't hurry!
What's his room number?
3B.
ありがとう
Thanks!
Hey, we got a suspicious male and female couple on the loose.
Er hey, we got a suspicious male and female couple on the loose.
I'm sending the pic from the security camera.
まいったなー
I give up...
I don't remember anything about this place.
全く覚えが無い
ここ俺の部屋か？
Is this really my room?
They fit!
ぴったり…
な、なんだ、こりゃ？
W-What the heck is this?!
テロリストのアジトかよ
It looks just like a terrorist's hideout!
What was it called? It's like in that movie...
なんだっけ、あの映画みたいだなぁ
Taxi Driver!
「タクシードライバー」！
だったら全裸じゃなくてもモヒカンだろ
I should have a mohawk rather than being naked, really...
Passports?
パスポート？
何冊あんだよ
Just how many do I have?
So, I'm not De Niro but Jason Bourne?
デ・ニーロじゃなくてジェーソン・ボーン？
They're all mine...
ん？ 全部俺って…
There's definitely a conspiracy behind this.
こりゃあ絶対誰かにハメられてんな
マジィ？！ 俺やっぱ、テロリスト？
Are you serious?!
We'll kill you!
I'm really a terrorist?
もしかして人とか殺してる？
Could it be that I've even killed someone before?
あ、あの、さっきコート貸した人ですよね
Um, you're the one I lent my coat to earlier, right?
Would you mind giving it back?
あれ、やっぱり返してもらってもいいですか
ポケットの中にパスポートとお財布が入れてあったんです
I left my passport and wallet in the pocket.
なんなら、コートはあげますから、それだけ返して！
It's okay if you want to keep the coat, but please give back the rest!
いいよ、ちょっと待ってて
Okay, just wait a minute.
Morimi Saki. Born in 1989?
森美 咲（もりみ・さき）…
1989年（せんきゅうひゃくはちじゅうきゅうねん）生まれか
これだ！ これがいい
This one! This one's good.
My name will be...
名前は… 滝沢 朗（たきざわ・あきら）…
Takizawa Akira...
よし、今から俺は滝沢朗だ！
Okay! From now on, I'll be Takizawa Akira!
What the heck is he doing... Hurry up!
何してんの？ 早くしてよ
Hello. I need to ask you something.
What's wrong?
何ですか？
The girl in this picture, is that you?
U-Um... T-That's...
あのー
Sorry to keep you waiting.
待たせたね
行こう
Let's go.
あ、あのー
U-Um...
Wait a sec...
Wait a sec.
Come this way, please.
Come this way please.
Are you Japanese?
I need to see your Johnny.
I need to see your johnny.
Woah!
これ、確かに俺っぽいけど、どこで撮られたんだろう？
He does look like me.
Where did you take that picture?
How's this? It's really me, right?
どうっすか！ やっぱ俺っすよね？
Oh!
Oh.
Thank you. Have a nice date.
あれ？ 人違い？
Oh? You got the wrong guy?
Bye then.
じゃあ、ご機嫌よう！
セーフ！
Phew! It's because it was freezing back then...
あの時は寒かったからね
急ごう、このままじゃやけくそだ
Let's go. The situation is going to get desperate soon.
何、やけくそって？
What do you mean by desperate?
With my luck, everything including the toilet will burn before we're out.
運が悪けりゃ、トイレまで全焼ってことさ
When are you going back to Japan?
君、いつ日本に帰るの？
今から帰るんですけど
I was just about to leave...
本当？
Really? Then let's go back together.
だったら一緒に帰ろうよ
Huh? Um... I'm...
えっ？ ちっ、ちょっと、あの、私…
何？
What's wrong?
I left my luggage behind before I came here.
ここに来る間に、カバンを置いてきちゃったんです
置いてきたのはさっきの場所？
Did you leave it where we were earlier?
Is there anything important in it?
何か重要なもの入ってる？
お土産とか、好きな洋服とか…
Just some souvenirs and clothes that I like...
なら、残念だけどあそこには戻らない方がいい
Well, it's a shame, but we probably shouldn't go back there.
Leave everything to me.
俺に任せて、タクシー代だけ貸してくれない？
Could you lend me some money for the taxi fare?
Come on, get in.
さあ、乗って
ほら
Hurry up.
警察に行ってくれ、大急ぎで
Take us to the police station.
It's urgent!
Why the police station?!
何で警察？！
I guess it's not a fake passport.
偽造パスポートじゃないんだ、一応
Here you go, your ticket and passport.
はい、チケットとパスポート
You seem used to traveling.
旅慣れてるんですね
Really?
そう？
大使館で飛行機の予約までしてもらうなんて、
内心ドキドキだったんですよ
You actually got the Embassy to book tickets for us.
I was really nervous.
もし嘘がバレたらって
If you got found out...
It wasn't a lie.
嘘なんてついてないじゃん
We went to make a police report about the theft first after all.
ちゃんと警察に盗難届けも出したし
でないと、大使館だって飛行機代は貸してくれないよ
Without that, the embassy wouldn't have lent us money to buy the plane tickets.
Government officials are actually quite heartless.
案外冷たいんだぜ、役人なんてさ
Really?
そうなんですか
If you look at what's happened, you've helped me out quite a lot.
あの…結果的には色々助けてもらった感じなんですけど
There's something that's been bothering me, though.
一つ気になってること聞いてもいいですか？
Mind if I ask you about it?
What is it?
何？
What were you trying to do when we first met?
最初に会ったとき、本当は何やってたんですか？
Were you involved in some kind of protest?
何かの抗議活動とか？
実は俺…テロリストなんだ
I'm actually a terrorist.
なんてね、うそ
Just kidding. That's a lie.
That's just a popular game played by overseas students here.
あれはこっちの留学生の間で流行ってるゲームなんだ
Pretty mean, right?
酷いだろ？ 玩具とはいえ、銃までも出されてさー
They made me bring a gun along, even though it's a toy.
ずいぶん過激なゲームなんですね
Quite an extreme game.
Yeah.
まあね
Why did you come to D.C.?
君は何でＤＣに来たの？
It's a graduation trip for my university.
大学の卒業旅行だったんです。
本当はニューヨークに…
I'm supposed to be in New York, but I really wanted to see the White House.
でも私、どうしてもホワイトハウスが見たくて途中から一人で
So I came here alone halfway through the trip.
Why did you want to see the White House?
なんでまたホワイトハウス？
How do I explain it... It's because it's the center of the world.
なんっていうか、一応あそこが世界の中心なのかなー、なんて
おかしいですよね？
Sounds weird, right?
普段はアメリカのことをそんなに意識しているわけじゃないのに
I don't normally care about America.
Somehow, though, I feel that everything,
私のちっちゃな悩みから世界情勢まで
from my small worries to the state of the world, comes from here.
根っこの部分では本当はみんなここに繋がっているのかな、
なんて思えてきて
Plus, don't you have this sinking feeling that Japan isn't able to do anything by itself?
でね、なんかあるじゃないですか？ 日本って、
もう自分たちじゃどうにもできない、重たい空気
I was thinking about making a wish,
それをね、少しでいいから何とかしてくださいって
お願いしてみようかな、なんて考えてたんです
hoping that something can be done to improve this situation a little.
So, I got in your way?
それを邪魔しちゃったわけだ
No. I knew my wish was impossible before I made it.
ううん。実際はその前に、それは無いなって
ここは私達と全然関係ないところなんだって
This place has nothing to do with us, after all.
I understand.
分かるよ
Even though I don't.
分かんないけど
What are you saying?!
なにそれ？！
However, some sense was knocked into me, thanks to someone's tiny  act of terrorism.
でも誰かさんがささやかなテロ行為で一矢報いてくれたから、
それでいいや
So, it's all fine.
My Johnny knocked some sense into you.
俺のジョニーが一矢報いた
I'm Morimi Saki.
私、森美咲です
俺は…
I'm...
This guy.
これ
滝沢朗さん？
Takizawa Akira-san...?
何？
What's wrong?
1989年１月７日（いちがつ・なのか）生まれ！
You were born on the 7th of January. You're just like me!
私と同じ！
You were born in the last 7 days of the Showa period,
平成に変わる直前の、昭和最後の７日間生まれ！
before it changed to Heisei!
I see, you're in the "64 Year Club" as well.
そうかあ、滝沢さんも６４年組（ろくじゅうよんねんぐみ）かー
But since you're born on the 7th of January, I'm older than you by a day.
でも１月７日だから、あたしのほうが一日お姉さんだ
Right, Takizawa-kun!
ね、滝沢君！
Could Takizawa-kun be my prince...?
滝沢君って、もしかしたらあたしの王子様？
そんなわけないか
That's impossible.
What's wrong?
どうしたの？
Is this what you meant by "sinking feeling?"
さっき君が言ってた重たい空気ってさ、
これのことかな？
東京にミサイル攻撃…
Tokyo was bombarded with missiles.
夜は封印
戸惑い混じれば終わる
迷い出すぐらいならいっそ
わ     け
理由も捨てよう
また夢に溺れる
不確かに続いてく未来
まだ君を許せる
意味を知れる
耳を澄ますための夜
その理由を真似て変われる
君の呼吸を知るために
未来の根を切っても構わない